Do it
222 how are you all and I
want to start today's video with a lot of information about which place
I am in which city is this and which
country is this in this video I have
given a look by looking at that look you can
understand what is the situation 129 now
which country or I want to tell you something today's
video is very important for all of you but
I can't sit here and make a bad video
because there is a lot of
noise here and I
want to share this important description
with you so I will go to my room and
press that
now it is so beautiful all night or it will
continue for two three four better so I wanted to ask
you an important
question and a lot of questions were
coming to me and let's how to go to
Gwalior and
definition of wali's facts related to this I will
leave the subscribe button above and all of you
replied
you
[music] I
live in subscribe I live in
so I had taken it I go to South India so
there  So
I did this just
because if you live in Nottingham or
elsewhere then maybe you can take the Pune Express
just for now. By far, we can take it a little
closer to the Priya distance, it's probably a little cheaper.
If you want to reduce your travel time, you can
go from South India to Saudi Arabia.
Otherwise, you can either go to Malaysia or Singapore if you have a VAT
number, but these can be
different.
I came from Bangalore, I was from Bangalore,
before Bangalore I was on the Shyamali Shashit Bali
committee, brother, and what is the transit
process? What is this? Let me tell you one more thing.
I was coming from Bangalore to Bari or
Malaysia, well, mine was also peaceful, but I did
n't have to give any transit visa
because the factory of the majors is on the same
side and there are banks on both sides from
Malaysia to Bali, so the factories of both the bills
and the same love increase,
so you do
n't need any extra transit direction, you
can easily travel if you are from home.  If you are
from any city, then if you are typing then you have to
see that it is on the same site, be it a
relationship or Malaysia Airlines
or a job or a message alliance, but it will need an egg
channel, so this will take a
lot of interruption and there will be no
problem in transiting very easily. The third
question asked was whether you have travel
insurance, so travel insurance is in
India and it has faced a lot of
situations, since then it has become more important,
you can get any work done in travel insurance
and Rice Strausskahn
medical is also covered, so this medical and
Gaurav Tower, but if your luggage is stuck or you have
burnt or you have
missed your flight, then
you are provided insurance for all that.
Intruded medical shop travel insurance,
now you will see the innings, then you have to
see that the
medical insurance is covering up to the tank,
tank doctors and 1000 more
and if
all the medical stores are giving the news themselves, then you will get it, then the
bank will
confuse you.  So this travel insurance
medical insurance 580 is
covered in it at all, so
I had taken ICICI, you
cannot lose your lines or
you can also get insurance by going to the policy market,
friends, I was asked at the time that it is
necessary to carry six towels, about this
your Indian Rupee will not be accepted or not, so
friends this will be accepted,
but if it is accepted in some places, I mean in most of the
places seriously okay and for festivals
I also did not use this, opposition message more than
₹ 2000, this is a sanskar, only the
women who were roaming inside, I got
under, so this was a little earlier Lord but exactly
this compound value is
193, right now if you look at the Aai Roy, then
180 is going on, but for a week you will
get 160 or 155 or 150
around this in the safe, so Aai Babuji goes
but she was something like this, click on the toilet
and if you do not want this I will be easy
for you and there is no problem that  You will
ask that important question, you are left behind
senior but artificial friend, when I came
then it was artificial but if you are fully
vaccinated then artificial is not being asked, it is
most important for you, this
definition certificate should be there and
both of them should be taken, if not then
in that case both will not be admitted,
in that case you will have to get artificial
if you are fully vaccinated, whether
it is any obscene or maximum then
you do not need to test anything,
you should directly go and
what was declared in the last sewerage, I want to
enter India, you should answer those questions in that,
Atharva Veda then covered the pan, he said that no
question was asked, when one thing was
asked that tell me do you have travel insurance, tell me is it
related to this, tell me
reduce return ticket and they will
ask such things, the dress that I went on a strange date,
only one question was asked from me that do you have
credit, that's all, nothing else was
asked from me, I was put on 19, so you  The
time it took to go through it, the
time it took me to understand was that the people were moving very slowly
and the immigration officers were sitting very few
and there were more people, so most of the time was spent
in continuous questioning,
judgment, if there was even a single question then
Bigg Boss would never ask Vijay ji
when are you returning and anything would happen, these were
all questions, I will ask a lot from your side,
I will make this video so that there will be
some communication
and we can understand it better, if I still
forget some topic then you can
ask the commissioner, I will request you to
reply to it a little bit, it is a very
good country, international and this is a very good
phone and the other one is very
beautiful, you please come and do extra, should you
come alone or should you
come with family and with water, so from
time to time you should take
care of yourself and your family,
okay and from here this family 10